(cooing)
(Howard:)Okay, here's the plan.
(Howard:)I'm gonna put the food
in the bag,
(Howard:)and when he lands in the bag
to eat it, we close it up.
(Leonard:)A Slim Jim?
(Howard:)It's all I could find.
It'll work.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Sure.
(Leonard:)If the pigeon's stoned
or a trucker.
(Howard:)Okay, well, what's your plan?
(Leonard:)I told you my plan.
(Leonard:)Let's call Building Services
and get help.
(Howard:)And admit that we contaminated
the clean room?
No, admit that you
contaminated the clean room.
(Howard:)Why do you keep assuming
it was me?
(Leonard:)Because you do this kind
of thing all the time,
(Leonard:)and then you try
to cover it up.
(Howard:)Like when?
(scoffs)
(Leonard:)What about when you
flipped the Mars Rover,
(Leonard:)or lost Koothrappali's dog,
(Leonard:)or almost drove off
with that baby?
(Howard:)Again, it looked like my car,
and the baby didn't even cry
(Howard:)until his mother punched me
with her keys.
(Leonard:)Fine, put the Slim Jim
in the garbage bag.
(Howard:)Well, what if you said it